<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.kde.kwordquiz.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>KWordQuiz</name>
  <name xml:lang="bs">KWordQuiz</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">KWordQuiz</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">KWordQuiz</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">KWordQuiz</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">KWordQuiz</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">KWordQuiz</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">KWordQuiz</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">KWordQuiz</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">KWordQuiz</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">KWordQuiz</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">KWordQuiz</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">KWordQuiz</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">KWordQuiz</name>
  <name xml:lang="ia">KWordQuiz</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">KWordQuiz</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">KWordQuiz</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">KWordQuiz</name>
  <name xml:lang="lt">KWordQuiz</name>
  <name xml:lang="nds">KWordQuiz</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">KWordQuiz</name>
  <name xml:lang="nn">KWordQuiz</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">KWordQuiz</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">KWordQuiz</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">KWordQuiz</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">KWordQuiz</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">KWordQuiz</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">KWordQuiz</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">KWordQuiz</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">KWordQuiz</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">KWordQuiz</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKWordQuizxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">KWordQuiz</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">語言_KWordQuiz</name>
  <summary>Flash Card Trainer</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="bs">Učitelj fleš karticama</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Entrenador amb targetes ràpides</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Entrenador amb targetes ràpides</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Procvičování slovní zásoby s kartičkami</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Karteikartentrainer</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="el">Εκπαιδευτής ερωτήσεων με κάρτες</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Flash Card Trainer</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Entrenador de tarjetas</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="et">Sähvikute treening</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Sanaston harjoittelu kysymyskorteilla</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Entraînement aux cartes mémoire</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Adestrador de vocabulario</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">Pelatihan Kartu Flash</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Apprendimento con carte mnemoniche</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">플래시 카드 트레이너</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="lt">Mokymasis iš kortelių</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nds">Koorten-Lehrprogramm</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Woorden oefenen</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nn">Spørsmålskort</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Ćwiczenie z fiszkami</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Treinador de Cartões</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Treinador de cartões</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Программа для изучения новой лексики</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Precvičovanie slovnej zásoby s kartičkami</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Učenje s spominskimi kartami</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Flash Card Trainer</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Fiş Çalıştırıcı</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Тренування словникового запасу</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxFlash Card Trainerxx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-CN">卡片式训练程序</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-TW">閃卡訓練師</summary>
  <description>
    <p>KWordQuiz is a general purpose flash card program. It can be used for vocabulary learning and many other subjects. It provides an editor and five different flashcard quiz modes. It uses the KVTML file format and contributed files can be downloaded from within the application.</p>
    <p xml:lang="bs">KWordQuiz je program opšte namjene fleš kartica. Može se koristiti za učenje riječi i s mnogim drugim temama. On pruža urednik i pet različitih flashcard kviz režima. Koristi format KVTML datoteke i doprinesni fajlovi mogu se preuzeti u okviru same aplikacije.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El KWordQuiz és un programa de targetes ràpides de finalitat general. Es pot utilitzar per a aprendre vocabulari i molts altres temes. Proporciona un editor i cinc modes diferents de targetes ràpides. Utilitza el format de fitxer KVTML i es poden baixar a l'aplicació fitxers de col·laboracions.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">El KWordQuiz és un programa de targetes ràpides de finalitat general. Es pot utilitzar per a aprendre vocabulari i molts altres temes. Proporciona un editor i cinc modes diferents de targetes ràpides. Utilitza el format de fitxer KVTML i es poden baixar a l'aplicació fitxers de col·laboracions.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">KWordQuiz ist ein universell einsetzbares Karteikartenprogramm. Es kann für das Vokabel lernen und viele andere Bereiche verwendet werden. Es bietet einen Editor und fünf verschiedene Karteikarten-Quiz-Modi. Es verwendet das KVTML-Dateiformat und beigetragene Dateien können aus der Anwendung heraus heruntergeladen werden.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Το KWordQuiz είναι ένα γενικού σκοπύ πρόγραμμα εκπαίδευσης με κάρτες. Χρησιμοποιείται για εκμάθηση λεξιλογίου και σε διάφορους άλλους τομείς. Περιλαμβάνει έναν επεξεργαστή και πέντε διαφορετικές λειτουργίες ερωτήσεων με κάρτες. Χρησιμοποιεί τον τύπο αποθήκευσης KVTML και μπορεί να γίνει λήψη αρχείων συνεισφοράς μέσα από την εφαρμογή.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">KWordQuiz is a general purpose flash card program. It can be used for vocabulary learning and many other subjects. It provides an editor and five different flashcard quiz modes. It uses the KVTML file format and contributed files can be downloaded from within the application.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">KWordQuiz es un programa de tarjetas de propósito general. Se puede utilizar para aprender vocabulario y otras muchas tareas. Proporciona un editor y cinco modos de tarjetas diferentes. Utiliza el formato de archivo KVTML y los archivos con los que han contribuido los usuarios se pueden descargar desde la aplicación.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">KWordQuiz on üldotstarbeline sähvikute rakendus. Seda saab kasutada sõnavara omandamiseks, aga veel paljuks muuks. Rakendus pakub redaktorit ja viit eri viisi korraldada sähvikute abil viktoriine. Failivorminguks on KVTML, mis lubab otse rakenduses alla laadida teiste kasutajate loodud huvitavaid faile.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">KWordQuiz on yleiskäyttöinen kysymyskorttiohjelma. Sitä voi käyttää sanastojen ja monen muun harjoittelemiseen. Siinä on muokkain ja viisi erilaista kyselytapaa. Se käyttää KVTML-tiedostomuotoa ja lahjoitettuja tiedostoja voi ladata suoraan ohjelmasta.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">KWordQuiz est un programme générique pour les cartes mémoire. Il peut être utilisé pour apprendre du vocabulaire et plein d'autres choses. Il fournit un éditeur et cinq modes de quiz différents. Il utilise le format de fichier KVTML et des extensions conformes à ce format peuvent être téléchargés à partir de l'application.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">KWordQuiz é un programa de fichas de propósito xeral. Pode usarse para adestrar vocabulario e para moitas outras cousas. Fornece un editor e cinco modos distintos de preguntas mediante fichas. Usa o formato de ficheiro KVTML e os ficheiros doados poden descargarse desde a propia aplicación.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">KWordQuiz adalah program kartu flash pada umumnya. Ini dapat digunakan untuk pembelajaran kosa kata dan banyak mata pelajaran lainnya. Ini menyediakan editor dan lima mode kuis flashcard yang berbeda. Ini menggunakan format file KVTML dan file kontribusi dapat diunduh dari dalam aplikasi.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">KWordQuiz è un programma di carte mnemoniche. Può essere usato per l'apprendimento di vocaboli e moltre altre materie. Fornisce un editor e cinque diversi tipi di quiz con carte menmoniche. Usa il formato di file KVTML e permette di scaricare file inviati da altri utenti.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">KWordQuiz는 플래시 카드 프로그램입니다. 단어 및 기타 다양한 학습 용도로 사용할 수 있습니다. 편집기와 다섯 가지 플래시 카드 모드를 지원합니다. KVTML 파일 형식을 사용하며 프로그램 내에서 다운로드할 수 있습니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nds">KWordQuiz is en allmeen Naslakoortprogramm. Du kannst dat för't Öven vun Wöör, man ok to anner Saken bruken. Dat hett en Editor un fief Affraag-Bedriefoorden. As Dateiformaat warrt dat KVTML-Formaat bruukt un vun Brukers bidragen Dateien laat sik binnen dat Programm daalladen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">KWordQuiz is een draaikaart programma voor algemene doeleinden. Het kan gebruikt worden voor het leren van woordjes en vele andere onderwerpen. Het biedt een editor en vijf verschillende manieren om draaikaarten te gebruiken. Het gebruikt het KVTML bestandsformaat en aanvullende bestanden kunnen gedownload worden vanuit de toepassing.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">KWordQuiz er eit program for øving med spørsmåls­kort. Det kan brukast til å utvida ordforrådet ditt eller til å læra ulike emne. Det har innebygd redigering av spørsmåls­kort og støttar fem ulike spørje­modusar. Det brukar filformatet KVTML, og du kan lasta ned spørsmåls­kort som andre har laga via programmet.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">KWordQuiz jest programem do ćwiczenia na fiszkach ogólnego przeznaczenia. Dostarcza edytor i pięć różnych trybów quizów na fiszkach. Program używa formatu plików KVTML, a pliki stworzone przez innych użytkowników można pobrać z wewnątrz programu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O KWordQuiz é um programa de cartões de uso geral. Poderá ser usado para a aprendizagem de vocabulário e para muitos outros assuntos. Oferece um editor e cinco modos diferentes de questionários por cartões. Ele usa o formato de ficheiros KVTML e os ficheiros contribuídos poderão ser transferidos a partir da aplicação.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">KWordQuiz é um programa de cartões de uso geral. Ele pode ser usado para aprendizagem de vocabulário e muitos outros assuntos. Oferece um editor e cinco modos diferentes de perguntas em forma de cartões. Ele usa o formato de arquivo KVTML e os arquivos disponibilizados por terceiros podem ser baixados a partir do aplicativo.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">KWordQuiz — программа для заучивания новых слов по системе Лейтнера, то есть с помощью карточек. Таким же образом в этой программе можно учить не только слова, но и например ответы на вопросы из различных областей знаний. В программу встроен редактор карточек. На ваш выбор есть пять режимов тренировки. Файлы сохраняются в формате KVTML. Готовые файлы, предоставленные другими пользователями KWordQuiz, можно загрузить прямо из программы.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">KWordQuiz je všeobecný kartový program. Dá sa použiť na učenie slovnej zásoby a na mnoho iných účelov. Obsahuje editor a 5 rôznych režimov kvízov s kartami. Používa formát súborov KVTML a súbory sa dajú stiahnuť priamo z aplikácie.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">KWordQuiz je splošen program za učenje s spominskimi kartami. Uporabite ga lahko za učenje besedišča in drugih zadev. Ponuja urejevalnik in pet različnih načinov kviza s spominskimi kartami. Uporabniško prispevane datoteke KVTML, ki jih uporablja, lahko prejmete znotraj programa.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Kwordquiz är ett generellt program för snabbkort. Det kan användas för inlärning av ordförråd och många andra ämnen. Det tillhandahåller en editor och fem olika frågemetoder för snabbkort. Det använder filformatet KVTML, och bidragna filer kan laddas ner inne i programmet.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">KWordQuiz genel amaçlı bir fiş çalıştırma programıdır. Kelime öğrenmek veya başka bir çok konu için kullanılabilir. Bir düzenleyici ve beş farklı fiş sınav kipi içerir. KVTML dosya biçimini kullanır ve katkı verilmiş dosyalar uygulama içinden indirilebilir.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">KWordQuiz — програма для навчання за допомогою карток загального призначення. Нею можна скористатися для поповнення словникового запасу іноземною мовою або вивчення інших дисциплін. У програмі передбачено редактор та п’ять різних режимів навчання за допомогою карток. Для даних використовується формат файлів KVTML, файли даних, створені іншими користувачами, можна отримати безпосередньо за допомогою програми.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKWordQuiz is a general purpose flash card program. It can be used for vocabulary learning and many other subjects. It provides an editor and five different flashcard quiz modes. It uses the KVTML file format and contributed files can be downloaded from within the application.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">KWordQuiz 是一套閃卡記憶訓練程式。它可以用於字彙學習，還有許多其它的用途。它提供了一個編輯器與五種不同的閃卡模式。它使用 KVTML 檔案格式，並且可以下載其他人所製作的閃卡檔。</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://edu.kde.org/kwordquiz/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=kwordquiz</url>
  <url type="help">https://docs.kde.org/?application=kwordquiz</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.kde.org/community/donations/?app=kwordquiz&amp;source=appdata</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>Flashcard quiz in KWordQuiz</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Qüestionari de targetes ràpides al KWordQuiz</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Qüestionari de targetes ràpides al KWordQuiz</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="cs">Kvíz s kartičkami v KWordQuiz</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Karteikartenquiz in KWordQuiz</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="el">Ερωτηματολόγιο με κάρτες στο KWordQuiz</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en-GB">Flashcard quiz in KWordQuiz</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Juego de tarjetas de KWordQuiz</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="et">Sähvikutega viktoriin KWordQuizis</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">KWordQuizin kysymyskorttivisa</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Questionnaire à cartes sur KWordQuiz</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gl">Proba de cartas en KWordQuiz</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="id">Kuis flashcard di KWordQuiz</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Quiz di carte mnemoniche in KWordQuiz</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ko">KWordQuiz의 플래시카드 퀴즈</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Flashkaart-toets in KWordQuiz</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nn">Spørjekort-kviss i KWordQuiz</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Fiszki w KWordQuiz</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Questionário com cartões no KWordQuiz</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt-BR">Modo de perguntas em cartões no KWordQuiz</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sk">Kvíz s kartami v KWordQuiz</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Kviz s spominskimi kartami KWordQuiz</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Snabbkortsprov i KWordQuiz</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Тест за допомогою карток у KWordQuiz</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxFlashcard quiz in KWordQuizxx</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-CN">KWordQuiz 中的抽认卡测试</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-TW">在 KWordQuiz 中測驗閃卡</caption>
      <image>https://kde.org/images/screenshots/kwordquiz.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>kwordquiz</binary>
  </provides>
  <releases>
    <release version="21.08.0" date="2021-08-12"/>
    <release version="21.04.3" date="2021-07-08"/>
    <release version="21.04.2" date="2021-06-10"/>
    <release version="21.04.1" date="2021-05-13"/>
  </releases>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>
</component>
